(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "h264_qsv"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
はぁ、今日も一人カラオケなのかな。
Sigh, am I doing solo karaoke again today?
おい、コメント一人カラオケに来たんじゃねえ、一人カラオケって言うんじゃねえよ。
Hey, I didn't come here for solo karaoke, so don't call it that!
2026年はコミュ症脱出するって言ったのに、なんでりおなまた一人なんだろう。
I said I'd escape my social anxiety in 2026, so why am I alone again?
せっかくマラカスも持ってきたのにさ。今日は先輩と一緒にさ、カラオケできると思って...
I even brought maracas... I thought I'd be able to do karaoke with my senpais today...
お助けカラオケ！
Rescue Karaoke!
あれ、先輩たち！
Oh, senpais!
ここでよかったのかな？
Was it okay to come here?
何してたの？何してたの？
What were you doing? What were you doing?
みんなで！お呼びだよ、みんなで今日カラオケしようよ。
Everyone! You're invited, let's all do karaoke today.
やったー！
Yay!
よろしくお願いします！
Please take care of me!
はい、よろしく！ということでね。
Yes, glad to! So then...
あれ、ねねち？
Wait, Nenechi?
あれ？なんか綺麗になってる！
Oh? You look... clean!
みんなのエナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねです！
Everyone's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene here!
なんかねねち綺麗になってる！
Wait, Nenechi, you look so clean!
綺麗になってる！やめろ！
You've become clean! Stop it!
浄化されてる！
She's been purified!
綺麗になってる、やめろ！
She's become clean, stop it!
善人の、善人桃鈴ねねです。
I'm the virtuous, virtuous Momosuzu Nene.
善人桃鈴ねね！
Virtuous Momosuzu Nene!
こんにちは。
Hello.
やったー、嬉しい！
Yay, I'm so happy!
嬉しいわ、ありがとう神様。
I'm happy too, thank you God.
さっき電話して、さっき来てくれたんだ。
I just called, and you just came.
さっき電話かかってきた。本当にさっき来た。
I just got the call. I really just got here.
本当にありがとう。ということで今日はこの四人でカラオケ楽しんでいきましょー！
Thank you so much. So, let's enjoy karaoke with the four of us today!
イェーイ！
Yay!
カラオケ久しぶりだな。
It's been a while since I did karaoke.
めっちゃタンバリン...
The tambourine is so...
タンバリン可愛い。
The tambourine is cute.
何も持ってないんだけど、装備大丈夫かな？
I don't have anything, is my equipment okay?
大丈夫。楽しむ気持ちがあれば。
It's fine. As long as you have the spirit of enjoyment.
そうそう。マイクを片手に持てば。
Exactly. Just hold the mic in one hand.
何も聞かされないまま来た。とりあえずカラオケ。
I came without being told anything. Karaoke for now.
とりあえずカラオケ来ない？みたいな。
Like, 'Want to just come to karaoke?'
よし、じゃあ、まずは一曲目。まつりから誘ったから、まつり歌っていい？
Alright, then, for the first song... Since I invited everyone, can I sing?
いいんじゃない！
Sure!
じゃあね、どうしようかな。これにしようかな、これにしようかなと思います。
Then, let's see... I think I'll go with this one. Yeah, this one.
どんな曲なんだろう。
I wonder what song it is.
よし。あ、マイク、マイク。
Alright. Oh, the mic, the mic.
マイクマイク。
Mic mic.
持った。盛り上げてよ。ちょ、ペンライト、ペンライト。
Got it. Cheer me on! Hey, penlights, penlights.
いいですね。
Nice.
よし、歌います。歌うます。
Alright, I'm singing! I'm singing!
頑張れ！
Good luck!
盛り上げてね。
Cheer me on!
はーい！
Okay!
じゃあ風真、ちょっとダダダダダダダって、ボボボボボボボボボかな。
Then Kazama, give me a 'da-da-da-da' or 'bo-bo-bo-bo'.
ねえ もっとちょうだい？
Hey, give me more?
:-b ;-b boy, :-b ;-b boy, duh
べー！
Bleh!
気付いてよ 履修してよ
Notice me, study me
あたしのこと とんとん
Focus on me, ton-ton
もー、べー！
Geez, bleh!
嫌いだよ 頭悪そうって顔するの
I hate it when you look at me like I'm stupid
のんのん
Non-non
さあ 勘繰りダンス ブギウギ
Now, speculative dance, boogie-woogie
迷子でぼっち デビデビ
Lost and lonely, devi-devi
感情をください ハイハイ
Give me your emotions, hai-hai
ぷー 配信ダンス ブギウギ
Poo, streaming dance, boogie-woogie
解釈一致 ギミギミ
Interpretation match, gimme-gimme
返答をください ハイハイ
Give me your response, hai-hai
「期待しないで」とか今更では？
Saying 'don't expect anything' now? Isn't it too late?
まじで STOP
Seriously, STOP
脈ナシハラスメント
No-pulse harassment
待ちに待った思春期頑張べ
Waiting and waiting, adolescent efforts
あいうぉんちゅーコールが聞こえなーい
I can't hear the 'I want you' call
伝播する義務ラブマッチング
Propagating compulsory love matching
要承認ハートのリハしたい
I want to rehearse this 'approval required' heart
ライブでは下手くそ やんなっちゃう
I'm so bad live, it's annoying
はぁ「恋愛ガールは叶えたい」
Sigh, 'Love Girl wants it to come true'
衝撃のアニメ化待っています
Waiting for the shocking anime adaptation
アンハッピーエンドじゃつまんない
An unhappy ending is boring
フィーチャリング “feat. きみ”を
Featuring 'feat. You'
ねえ もっとちょうだい？
Hey, give me more?
:-b ;-b boy, :-b ;-b boy, duh
ねえ 気付いても 無視するとこ そういうとこ
Hey, even if you notice, you ignore me, that part of you
ねえ 嫌いだと思えるほど強くないの
Hey, I'm not strong enough to think I hate you
さあ テンパリトーク ドギマギ
So let's, flustered talk, panic,
ハードなチャンス デビデビ
hard chance, devi-devi,
思えるほど 強くないの
I'm not as strong as I seem.
さあ テンバリトーク ドギマギ ハードなチャンス デビデビ
So let's, flustered talk, panic, hard chance, devi-devi,
原稿をください ハイハイ
give me the draft, high-high!
さあ ギャンブルトーク ドギマギ 恋＄ベット デビデビ
So let's, gamble talk, panic, love $ bet, devi-devi,
全勝をください ハイハイ
give me total victory, high-high!
さあ ギャンブルトーク ドギマギ 恋＄ベット
So let's, gamble talk, panic, love $ bet,
全勝をください ハイハイ
give me total victory, high-high!
わあああああははは！？ まじでSTOP
Waaaaaah!? Seriously, STOP!
逆張りハラスメント
Contrarian harassment.
勝ちに行って負けるの何回目
How many times have I gone for the win and lost?
嫌になんぜ
I'm getting sick of it.
あいうぉんちゅーコール
I want you call,
伝わんない
it's not getting through,
飽和するテレパシザッピング
saturated telepathy zapping.
妄想継承してリベンジャー
Inheriting delusions, revenger,
先帝の無念晴らしてやる
I'll avenge the previous emperor's regret.
はぁ「転生したらあたしだった」 大好きの壁打ちやっています
Hah, "I was me when I reincarnated," I'm practicing rallies for my favorites.
アンハッピーエンドじゃつまんない
An unhappy end is boring,
"feat. きみ" を ねえもっとちょうだい！
give me more "feat. you"!
:-D Duh yeah, :-D Duh yeah
あいうぉんちゅーコールが
The "I want you" call...
聞こえなーい
I can't hear it!
アンハッピーエンドじゃつまんない
An unhappy end is boring,
"feat. きみ" を
..."feat. you,"
ねえもっとちょうだい！
come on, give me more!
「テレパシーザッピング」ですね！
That was "Telepathy Zapping"!
ですねー！
It sure was!
おっしゃ！じゃあ次誰行く？
Alright! Who's next?
後輩待ってるよ。
The juniors are waiting.
すごい！2曲目ね！
Amazing! Second song!
2曲目ね。最初からぶち上げさから。
Second song. Starting with a bang.
ぶち上がる！ぶち上がってた、あったまってる会場！
Hyped! It was hyped, the venue is warmed up!
歌う？
Wanna sing?
歌おう歌おう歌おう！
Let's sing, let's sing, let's sing!
なんでもいいよ、1番。
Anything's fine, pick one.
1番、いいですよ。
Number one is fine.
行ってるのに、ここに居たのに、楽しみにしてたのに！
I was going, I was here, I was looking forward to it!
はい、次行こうよ、次次次。
Okay, let's go next, next, next.
何に入れる？何に入れる？
What should I pick?
全然分かそうとしてただけ。
I was just trying to understand.
マラカス置いて、マイクを持ってじゃないの。
Put down the maracas and hold the mic.
違う違う、えーどれにしよう。
No no, uh, which one...
何がいい？
What's good?
えーどうしよう。
Uh, what should I do?
なんか、しっとり行きすぎ？一曲目から。
A bit too mellow? For the first song.
これ？これ？
This one? This one?
いいよ、全然いいよ。
Sure, totally fine.
え、歌えるかなー。
Eh, wonder if I can sing it.
じゃあこれにしようかな。
Then I'll go with this one.
緊張する。叩けるかな？ドラム。
I'm nervous. Can I play it? Drums.
まつりもサイリウム持つか。
I'll hold a light stick too.
歌うか！
Let's sing!
よし、歌って歌って！岩見先輩の前で恐縮らんですが。
Alright, sing! I'm nervous in front of Iwanami-senpai.
え？なんだ？
Eh? What?
おおー！なんだ？
Ooh! What?
え、立ったほうがいい？
Eh, should I stand up?
立ったほうがいいでしょ！お立ち台とか。
You should stand up! Like a podium.
お立ち台！？うわー！
Podium!? Whoa!
え、台になろうか？
Eh, should I become the stand?
一番乗りで Fly me to the moon
Being the first one there, Fly me to the moon
飛び込んできて Fly me to the moon
Come diving in, Fly me to the moon
あなただけに Fly me to the moon
Only for you, Fly me to the moon
うわー！すごーい！
Whoa! Amazing!
めっちゃ緊張したー！うまっ！
I was so nervous! That was so good!
かっこいい！すごい！
So cool! Awesome!
音大丈夫だった？
Was the sound okay?
あ、もうちょっとあげる？
Ah, should I turn it up a bit?
もうちょっとあげたほうがいいかな？
Maybe I should turn it up more?
声をもうすこしください。お願いします。
A little more voice, please. Thank you.
あー、緊張しない！
Ah, don't be nervous!
じゃ、次。次どうします？
Okay, next. What should we do next?
JTCちゃん、何がいいかな？
JTC-chan, what would be good?
じゃ、12に。12？
Then, let's go with 12. 12?
じゃあ、12で。ピピっと。
Okay, 12 it is. *Beep beep*
今から盛り上がってもいいんですか？マイク持って！
Is it okay to get hyped now? Grab the mic!
サイリウム持って！
Grab your lightsticks!
Sit up 姿勢正して
Sit up, straighten your posture
ひねくれた態度じゃ 不合格です
With that twisted attitude, you're failing
不幸中の幸いは 飽きてしまうわ
I'll get bored of the silver lining in this misfortune
Get up 目を覚まして
Get up, wake up
いい加減な言いなりに 黙ってうなづいてちゃ
Just nodding silently to careless obedience
No, no, no 伸び代がないわ
No, no, no, there's no room for growth
I got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 Things on my mind
思考 一向にまとまらない What do I do
My thoughts won't come together at all, what do I do
Running I'm running away 追いかける yesterday
Running, I'm running away, chasing yesterday
決める覚悟 迷いは捨て
Decide to decide, discard the hesitation
'Cause it's gonna hurt more The longer you wait
駆け引きなんていらない Say whatcha wanna say
I don't need any mind games, say whatcha wanna say
憂鬱なマンデー 気分はブルー
Melancholy Monday, feeling blue
痛みを噛んで 削ぎ剥がす
Biting the pain, stripping it away
古びた BANDAGE いらない
I don't need this old BANDAGE
Do whatcha wanna do
Man up 情けないね
Man up, how pathetic
言い訳ばかり Conversation もう勘弁
Nothing but excuses, this conversation, give me a break
つまずくの恐れちゃ どこもいけないわ
If you're afraid of stumbling, you can't go anywhere
Stand up 世は罠だらけ
Stand up, the world is full of traps
歯を見せれば 見せさせられる Nightmare?
If you show your teeth, they'll make you show them, nightmare?
無感情になれるなら 教えて頂戴
If I can become emotionless, please tell me how
Tell me A B C D E F G 正解のライン
Tell me A B C D E F G, the line of correctness
言葉選び出せない What do I do
I can't choose the words, what do I do
Finding I'm finding a way 追いかける One more day
Finding, I'm finding a way, chasing one more day
決める覚悟 迷いは捨て
Decide to decide, discard the hesitation
'Cause it's gonna hurt more The longer you wait
駆け引きなんていらない Say whatcha wanna say
I don't need any mind games, say whatcha wanna say
憂鬱なマンデー 気分はブルー
Melancholy Monday, feeling blue
痛みを噛んで 削ぎ剥がす
Biting the pain, stripping it away
古びた BANDAGE いらない
I don't need this old BANDAGE
Do whatcha wanna do
また見て見ぬふりの繰り返し ズタボロな心を
Repeating turning a blind eye again, my heart is in tatters
誰かのせいばかりしたって 何も変わりはしないの
Even if I just keep blaming someone else, nothing will change
負った傷口も 瘡蓋に いつかは剥がれ落ちて
The wounds I've suffered will scab over and one day peel away
Sorry not so sorry 選んだ Story
Sorry, not so sorry, the story I chose
自分次第でしょ
It's up to me, right?
決める覚悟 迷いは捨て
Decide to decide, discard the hesitation
'Cause it's gonna hurt more The longer you wait
駆け引きなんていらない Say whatcha wanna say
I don't need any mind games, say whatcha wanna say
憂鬱なマンデー 気分はブルー
Melancholy Monday, feeling blue
痛みを噛んで 削ぎ剥がす
Biting the pain, stripping it away
古びた BANDAGE いらない
I don't need this old BANDAGE
Do whatcha wanna do
イェーイ！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
やばい！あ、可愛い！
Oh my god! Ah, so cute!
最初読めなかったよ。
I couldn't read it at first.
めちゃめちゃ日本語上手い！
Your Japanese is so good!
漢字まずい…
Kanji is hard...
流石ですよ。
As expected of you.
すごいでも。
But it's amazing.
でもやっぱり英語の発音がかっきーな！
But your English pronunciation is really cool!
めちゃめちゃ上手い！
It's so good!
そうなんだよね！
Yeah, exactly!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7... みたいな。Rの発音がすげえ。
Like 'one, two, three...' Your 'R' pronunciation is awesome.
天才すぎた。これが生身の英語。
You're a genius. This is real-life English.
本場の英語。
Authentic English.
あれだ、風真次行きますか？
Alright, shall Kazama go next?
何歌いますか？
What will you sing?
え？何歌お？何がいい？
Eh? What should I sing? What would be good?
突然来たからカラオケの体で来てないんだよね私。
It was so sudden, I'm not really in a karaoke mood yet.
確かに。盛り上げるよ、任せなさい。
True. I'll get the crowd hyped, leave it to me.
はい、もう何だって致しますから。え、でもこれ歌ってほしい。
Yes, I'll do whatever it takes. Oh, but I want you to sing this.
じゃ、19にしようかな…
Then, maybe I'll go with 19...
お！来た！いいですね！
Oh! Here it comes! Nice!
絶対いい！絶対よくて実は…絶対いいそれは！
It's definitely good! Actually, it's great... definitely that one!
何を…あれ？俺のマイク？あ、これかも…これか？どれだっけ？
What... huh? My mic? Ah, maybe this one... this one? Which was it?
あ、これだぜだ。うん。
Ah, this is it. Yeah.
あ、ごめん。大丈夫。いろは先輩のマイク取っちゃった。
Ah, sorry. It's okay. I took Iroha-senpai's mic by mistake.
ござる殿のマイク上げたいけどな…よし！歌ってください！
I want to give you the mic but... alright! Please sing!
座って歌う派？あ、立ちます。
Do you sing sitting down? Ah, I'll stand.
立って歌う派。走った方がいいかな？
Singing standing up. Should I run?
晴る / n-buna
Haru / n-buna
貴方は風のように
You are like the wind
目を閉じては夕暮れ
If I close my eyes, it's dusk
何を思っているんだろうか
I wonder what you are thinking about
目蓋を開いていた
I was opening my eyelids
貴方の目はビイドロ
Your eyes are like glass
少しだけ晴るの匂いがした
I smelled a little bit of clear weather
これが晴るの匂い！怖い怖い！
This is the smell of spring! Scary, scary!
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け
Clear up, clear up, let the flowers bloom
咲いて晴るのせい
It's all spring's doing that they bloom
降り止めば雨でさえ
Even the rain, when it stops
貴方を飾る晴れ
Will make you shine in the sunlight
胸を打つ音よ風よ
Playing the stirring sounds in our hearts, oh wind
僕ら晴る風
We go like the spring wind
あの雲も越えてゆく
Go beyond the clouds too
遠くまだ遠くまで
Far, still far
貴方は晴れ模様に
You are like clear weather
目を閉じては青色
If I close my eyes, it's blue
何が悲しいのだろうか
What is it that is sad?
目蓋を開いている
I was opening my eyelids
貴方の目にビイドロ
Your eyes are like glass
今少し雨の匂いがした
I smelled a little bit of rain just now
これか…雨の香り…怖い！
This is it... the scent of rain... Scary!
泣きに泣け、空よ泣け
Cry, cry, let the sky cry
泣いて雨のせい
It's all the rain's fault
降り頻る雨でさえ
Even the pouring rain
雲の上では晴る
Above the clouds, it's clear
土を打つ音よ鳴れ
Let the sound striking the earth ring out
僕ら晴る荒れ
We are a spring storm
あの海も越えてゆく
Go beyond the sea too
遠くまだ遠くまで
Far, still far
うめぇ！ありがとうございます！すっごい匂い…怖いよ！
So good! Thank you! Such a strong scent... Scary!
通り雨草を靡かせ
Passing rain, making the grass sway
羊雲あれも春のせい
Sheep clouds, it's all spring's doing
風のように胸に春乗せ
Let the heart sway like the wind
晴るを待つ
Waiting for clear weather
晴れに晴れ、空よ裂け
Clear up, clear up, let the sky split
裂いて春のせい
It's all spring's doing that it splits
降り止めば雨でさえ
Even the rain, when it stops
貴方を飾る晴れ
Will make you shine in the sunlight
貴方を飾る晴る
You adorn the spring
胸を打つ音楽で 僕ら春風
With music that strikes the chest, we are the spring breeze
音に聞く晴るの風
The spring breeze heard in the sound
さぁ この歌よ 風げ！
Come, blow this song away!
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け
Brightly, brightly, flowers bloom
咲いて春のせい
Bloom, it's the spring's fault
あの雲も越えてゆけ
Go beyond those clouds too
遠く まだ遠くまで
Far, even further away
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
マジ何？描きすぎだろ！
Wait, what? You're writing too much!
描きすぎ！描きすぎ！
Too much! You're writing too much!
助かった、命があったわ
That helped, I'm still alive
何を描いてらっしゃったんだ
What on earth were you writing?
いい仕事したぜ
I did a good job
めっちゃ描かれてたんですが
It was being written all over the place
春の香りがしたわ
I smelled the scent of spring
春感じたな
I really felt the spring
後ろ 後ろ！
Behind you, behind you!
次ちょっと難しい歌歌っちゃおうかな
Maybe I'll sing a slightly difficult song next
歌えなかったら助けてくれる？
Will you help me if I can't sing it?
分かりました！
Understood!
難しい歌？
A difficult song?
行きます！
Here I go!
寿司食べたい！ Yeah!
I want to eat sushi! Yeah!
寿司食べたい！ ハイ！
I want to eat sushi! Yes!
寿司食べたい！ ホー！
I want to eat sushi! Ho!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
A primitive man with the 7th sense
6するこの世界と全人類
Rocking this world and all of humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
With us five, the game is changed
唸る4輪 発射せよ
Roaring four wheels, launch!
皆さん 3キュー サランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, I love you
操る2台のTurntable
Manipulating two turntables
獲る1番ここ Ground 0 (Ayo)
Taking the number one spot right here at Ground Zero (Ayo)
リスク超えて挑戦
Pushing beyond the risk, challenge
チャンスもセットだ当然
Naturally, the chance is part of the set
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the top
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking cushions like on Shoten
乗り込む FG ROADSTER
Boarding the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合能力者
A special unit gathering of the gifted
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into this history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving the following cars in the dust
今高速でぶち抜いていく
Now breaking through at high speed
大気圏
The atmosphere
エンジンからジェットの炎
Flames of jet from the engine
揺れている怪気炎
A shaking mysterious flame
眼下に広がる大地を
Over the earth spreading below
越えていく回帰線
Going across the Tropic
バックミラーに Big Blue が
With the Big Blue in the rearview mirror
写っている IBM (Fire!)
Reflected is IBM (Fire!)
打ち上げ台から飛んでいく
Flying off from the launch pad
うちら世代 この燃料
Our generation, this fuel
朽ち果てないです銀河で
Will never rot away in the galaxy
でかいビジョン燃えてる
A huge vision is burning
寿司食べたい見えてる
The sushi I want to eat is in sight
メンバー一同ただいま
All members, we're back
現在進行形
Currently in progress
超えていく世界規模
Going beyond the world scale
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It should come true, Won't stop
心臓がモンスター
My heart is a monster
Aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光る TESLA ROADSTER
Shining TESLA ROADSTER
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Instinct is waking up
青い炎 (Woo! Woo!)
Blue flame (Woo! Woo!)
BFF let's go out
so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unfettered from zero to space
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
唸る Booster
Roaring Booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me
Now Chase me
ターボ付きスーパーカー
Supercar with a turbo
副操縦士はチューバッカ
The co-pilot is Chewbacca
ハンドル捌きはシューマッハ
Steering wheel handling is Schumacher
次元が違う連中ばっか (Ayo)
Just a bunch from a different dimension (Ayo)
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Pushing the corners to the limit
モーター全開地響き
Motor at full throttle, earth shaking
空から導き お肌がピチピチ
Guidance from the sky, skin so bouncy
タイヤ焦がしてドーナッツターン
Burning tires, donut turn
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Popping and flying drum cans
顧客満足度高くて
Customer satisfaction is high
ぶち上がってるお客さん
Customers are hyped up
0から最高到達点
From zero to the highest point reached
ためめる太陽光発電
Storing solar power generation
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ
Entering super-awakening bonus stage
一直線伸びてる道路
A road extending in a straight line
速度増し上がってる高度
Increasing speed, rising altitude
限界、重力、凌駕し上昇
Exceeding limits and gravity, ascending
開拓しまくってくフロンティア
Conquering the frontier
旅立つ ROADSTER only one
Departure ROADSTER, only one
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the gas perfectly
1億馬力の重低音
100 million horsepower heavy bass
飛んでく日本遺産
Flying over Japan's heritage
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars is the rest stop
並んで走行 UFO
Flying side by side with UFOs
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing at the space station
物語を継承 (Ayo) まるで
Inheriting the story (Ayo) just like
旧約聖書 (Ayo) この先
The Old Testament (Ayo) ahead
何世紀も成長 生き延びて
Growing for centuries, surviving
結果出す Take off
Producing results, Take off
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It should come true, Won't stop
心臓がモンスター
My heart is a monster
Aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光る TESLA ROADSTER
Shining TESLA ROADSTER
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Instinct is waking up
青い炎 (Woo! Woo!)
Blue flame (Woo! Woo!)
BFF let's go out
so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unfettered from zero to space
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
唸る Booster
Roaring Booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me
Now Chase me
かわいい！
So cute!
フルロードした。そうそう。あれも好きなんだけどね。
It fully loaded. Yeah, yeah. I like that too, though.
あの、新しいさ。
You know, the new one.
MAKE IT BREAK IT! MAKE IT BREAK IT!
それそれ、それやめましょうもう。さっきのバーバーバーバー...
That, that, let's stop that already. The 'ba ba ba ba' from before...
それ何？ それ何なの？ あれ、こんな振りだよね？
What's that? What even is that? Wait, isn't that the dance?
出たダメだよ。泡の間ダメだ。
No, you can't go out. Bubbles are no good.
バーバーバーバーバー... 何それ？
Ba ba ba ba ba... What is that?
ちょ、何？ やってよ。MAKE IT BREAK IT. MAKE IT BREAK IT.
Wait, what? Do it. MAKE IT BREAK IT. MAKE IT BREAK IT.
MAKE IT BREAK IT. バーバーバーバー。好きに撃てい。
MAKE IT BREAK IT. Ba ba ba ba. Shoot however you like.
あ、じゃあこれでいっか。きゃあ！ いやだ！ やめて！
Ah, then this is fine. Eek! No! Stop it!
あれはダメだよ。
That's no good.
いやだ、それなしで。なるほどね。
No, without that. I see.
誰に言ってるんだろう？ あれだよね。いつか踊る機会があったら...
Who are you saying that to? That's right. If there's a chance to dance...
好きに撃つわ。じゃあ次、誰歌う？ はい。はい。
I'll shoot however I like. Okay, who's singing next? Me. Me.
今、寿司食べちゃった。寿司食べた？
I just ate sushi. You ate sushi?
寿司食べたくなっちゃった。寿司食べちゃった。
Now I want to eat sushi. I ate sushi.
誰がいいかな？ 何歌う？ お、どっちか歌う？
I wonder who should go? What will you sing? Oh, will one of you go?
どっち歌う？ どっち歌う？
Which one will sing? Which one will sing?
あ、いいよ。どっち歌う？ 何がいい？
Ah, sure. Which one will sing? What's good?
聴きたいな。何歌うのかな？
I want to hear. I wonder what they'll sing?
じゃあ10番。10番！ 10番、おい！
Okay, track 10. Track 10! Track 10, hey!
かわいいよ、10番の声。だって超... てれてれ。
Cute, the voice of track 10. Because it's so... shy, shy.
よかった。何か、この息が... これで暴れすぎて... 全力でやったよね。
That was good. This breath... I went too wild with this... I did it with all I had.
暴れちゃったから。
Because I went too wild.
さあ、サイリウム持って。よし、オタクするか。
Okay, get your glowsticks. Alright, let's go full otaku.
オタクでも... どうしようかな。まつりサイリウム置こ。
Even for otaku... what should I do. Matsuri, put down the glowstick.
きっとこの恋は少し甘くて たまに苦くて割れてしまいそう
I’m sure this love is a little sweet, and sometimes bitter, like it’s about to break
不器用なハート壊して チョコレートテンション
Breaking my clumsy heart, chocolate tension
冷たいミルクに溶かして いっそゴクンとしてしまえば
Dissolving it into cold milk, if I just go ahead and gulp it down
少しは良くなるかな
Maybe I’ll feel a little better
丸くなったこの心は あなたと目が合うたび また
This heart of mine that’s grown soft, every time our eyes meet, once again
頬を赤く染めるの すぐにそらしちゃうけど
My cheeks are dyed a bright red, even though I look away right away
駆け引きはもういいから 早く素直になってよ もう
I’m done with the mind games, so please, just be honest with me already
摩訶不思議な引力で うまく離れないみたい
With this mysterious gravity, it feels like I can’t pull away
言いたいことは山ほどあるのに 言えることは少しだけなの
Even though there’s a mountain of things I want to say, the things I can actually say are so few
いつまで経っても進めない
No matter how much time passes, I can’t move forward
このわだかまりをすぐ解けるのは あなた以外にはいないから
The only one who can clear up this hesitation is you and no one else
早く気づいてよね
So please, notice me soon
きっとこの恋は少し甘くて たまに苦くて割れてしまいそう
I’m sure this love is a little sweet, and sometimes bitter, like it’s about to break
不器用なハート壊して チョコレートテンション
Breaking my clumsy heart, chocolate tension
冷たいミルクに溶かして いっそゴクンとしてしまえば
Dissolving it into cold milk, if I just go ahead and gulp it down
少しは良くなるかな
Maybe I’ll feel a little better
もう考えすぎて頭はゴチャゴチャ ついでにモヤモヤ 最後はフヤフヤ
I’ve thought about it too much and my head is a mess, and on top of that, I’m feeling hazy, in the end, I’m just feeling weak
チョコより先に私が溶けそう もうあなたのせいよ 全部全部
It feels like I’m going to melt before the chocolate does, it’s all your fault, every bit of it
あなたがくれる最高の日々は 時々雨も付き物だけど
The wonderful days you give me sometimes come with a bit of rain
傘をさしてくれるのもあなた
But you’re the one who holds the umbrella for me
会いたい気持ち溢れ出したから 明日は特大のサプライズ
My feelings of wanting to see you have overflowed, so tomorrow, there’s a giant surprise
楽しみにしてるね
I’m looking forward to it
きっとこの恋は少し深くて たまに浅くてわかんないや
I’m sure this love is a little deep, and sometimes shallow, I just don’t know
不確かな心理に迫って 甘いシチュエーション
Approaching this uncertain state of mind, a sweet situation
素敵な笑顔でくしゃっと 私だけに ねぇ笑ってよ
With that lovely, crinkly smile, hey, won’t you smile just for me?
それだけでいいからさ お願い
That’s all I need, please
ありがとう！
Thank you!
こんな曲だっけ？
Was the song like this?
やべ、暴走してたことない？ ありがとう！
Bad, wasn't it totally out of control? Thank you!
きっとこの恋は少し甘くて
Surely this love is a little sweet
たまに苦くて割れてしまいそう
Sometimes bitter and likely to break
不器用なハート壊して
Breaking my clumsy heart
チョコレートテンション
Chocolate tension
冷たいミルクに溶かして
If I melt it into cold milk
いっそゴクンとしてしまえば
And just swallow it whole
少しは良くなるかな
Will it be a little better?
この恋は少し深くて
This love is a little deep
たまに浅くてわかんないや
Sometimes shallow and I don't get it
不確かな心理に迫って
Approaching an uncertain state of mind
甘いシチュエーション
Sweet situation
素敵な笑顔でぐしゃっと
With a lovely smile, crush it
私だけにねえ笑ってよ
Hey, smile only for me
それだけでいいからさ
That's all I need
甘い夢を見させて
Let me dream a sweet dream
いいよー！見せてるよー！
It's good! I'll show you!
かわいいー！待ってるー！
So cute! I'm waiting!
かわいいー！うまい！
So cute! You're good!
かわいいねー！ありがとう！
How cute! Thank you!
危ないよ！危ないよ！
It's dangerous! It's dangerous!
いいもの見せてもらった
I got to see something great.
かわいかったなー
That was cute.
すごいとこ来ちゃったなー
We've come to a crazy place.
鼻血が出ると思ったです ちょっと興奮してきたな
I thought I'd get a nosebleed. I'm getting excited.
ちょっと興奮してきたからここで…
I'm getting a bit excited, so right here...
ぜぜぜ！王様ゲーム！
Ze ze ze! The King's Game!
王様ゲーム？やったことないです！
The King's Game? I've never played it!
ガチで聞いてない！王様ゲーム？
Seriously, I haven't heard this! King's Game?
確かに風真は急遽だから何も言ってないけど
True, Kazama was a last-minute addition, so I didn't tell her.
王様ゲーム！誰も聞いてないし！
King's Game! No one heard about this!
ここにあの、王様ゲームできるものがありますので
I have something here to play the King's Game with.
みんなにはこれを一本ずつ引いてもらって
I'll have everyone pull one of these each.
赤いものがついてたら王様になることができます
If it has a red mark, you become the King.
これまつが王様だったらライン越える？怖い怖い！
If Matsu is the King, will she cross the line? Scary!
1から3まで数字があるんで、その指示をしてください
There are numbers 1 to 3, so please give instructions.
はい、じゃあ好きなもの。風真から引いていいよ
Okay, pick one. Kazama, you can go first.
これ？はい、じゃあゼータ
This one? Okay, next Zeta.
しょうがないな。これにしよう
Oh well. I'll take this one.
王様だーれだ！ゼーーターー！
Who is the King? It's Zeta!
ゼータ王様だ！何でも言うこと聞くので
Zeta is the King! We'll do whatever you say.
この3人が数字を言って… ゼータなら安心できる
The three of us will call out numbers... I feel safe with Zeta.
じゃあ、1番と… 1番は2番に…
Then, Number 1 and... Number 1 will...
1番は2番に、ほっぺちゅー！
Number 1, give Number 2 a kiss on the cheek!
なんで！？1番だーれだ！
Why!? Who is Number 1!?
ゼータ！？せっかく当たったからさ
Zeta!? Because I finally won.
1番はどっち？1番はだれ？
Which one is Number 1? Who is Number 1?
僕1番で！ぼたんちゃん2番で！
I'm Number 1! And Botan-chan is Number 2!
おおお！いただきます！いただきます！
Ooh! I'll take that! I'll take that!
ひえー！頑張れ！頑張れ！ほっぺにちゅー！
Whoa! Good luck! Good luck! Kiss on the cheek!
もうちょっとこの辺まで来てほしい。ちゅって言って
I want you to come a bit closer here. Say 'chuu'.
ちゅっ！あーー！何だこれ！
Chu! Ahh! What is this!?
うわーー！風真にはありと思います！
Whoa! I think it works for Kazama!
笑っちゃう！大惨事だ！
I can't stop laughing! It's a disaster!
ダメージが凄そうだけど
The damage looks high though.
えー！代打できたばかりこんなことになってんだよ！
Ehh! I just stood in as a sub and now this happens!
大丈夫、風真。洗顔したから大丈夫。
It's okay, Kazama. I washed my face, so it's fine.
大丈夫、風真。風真が次で王様になればいいだけだから
It's okay, Kazama. You just need to be the King next time.
確かに。王様だったら言うこと聞かなくていいんだよ
True. If you're the King, you don't have to listen to anyone.
でも王様側も難しいよね、これ。
But being the King is also difficult, isn't it?
何ですかこれは. はいはいはい、どうぞ。
What is this? Yes, yes, go ahead.
じゃあ、右端. はい右端ね。
Then, the far right. Okay, the far right.
じゃあ風真一番左端. じゃあ私これ。
Then Kazama the far left. I'll take this one.
行くよ、せーの！王様だーれだ！はーい！
Here we go, ready! Who is the King? Me!
おーゼーター！まつり様だ！
Oh, Zeta! It's Matsuri-sama!
どうしようかな？王様にもなれきるからね
What should I do? Since I can really be a King.
また3番が王様に. なるほど、そういうこと？
Number 3 is the King again. I see, is that how it works?
どうしようかな、本当に地獄にしよう。
What to do... I'll really make it hell.
地獄！？頼むよマジで！
Hell!? Please, seriously!
一番後輩だからな！やってやるよ！
I'm the youngest! I'll do it!
3番の人が、0歳の生まれ… 生まれた時からの
The person who is Number 3, starting from age 0...
一生をここに、こうやって語ってください
tell the story of your entire life right here like this.
だからさ、３番なんだよ！
I'm telling you, it's number three!
踊ってるよ！踊ってるよ！
She's dancing! She's dancing!
０歳からね、１００歳まで。
From zero years old to a hundred.
愛嬌上手、愛嬌上手！
So charming, so charming!
別にメガネとか好きじゃないですけど。
It's not like I like glasses or anything.
王様だー！やったー！
It's the King! Yay!
真ん中に１番立っていただいて。
Have number one stand in the middle.
愛の囁きをね、ＡＳＭＲリアルへ...
A real ASMR whisper of love...
みんなのこと、大好きだよ。
I love you all.
ねえちゃん... 愛してるよ。
Big sister... I love you.
先輩、毎日クッキー作ってあげますね。
Senpai, I'll bake cookies for you every day.
いきます
Let's go!
せーの
Ready, set...
王様だーれだ！
Who's the King?!
王様だー!
I'm the King!
よっしゃー！ オッケーオッケー よかったー
Yes! Okay, okay! That was good!
すごいね やらせなしで すごいすごい
Amazing, no scripting! Amazing, amazing!
王様って何を頼むんだい？
What does the King order?
頼むのも難しいですからね 王様ゲーム
It's hard to order things in King's game.
いいなー なんでも
Anything is fine.
えー じゃあ...
Uh, then...
めっちゃ迷うな
I'm really torn.
ASMRやってあげたって
Do some ASMR for them.
大丈夫です
I'm fine.
無理やり耳とか舐めるけど
I'll force-lick your ears though.
えー!?
Eh?!
大丈夫です
I'm fine.
断られた
I got rejected.
あ、じゃあ1番の人は
Oh, then person number 1...
いろは先輩 かっこいいって言ってもらって
Say 'Iroha-senpai is cool'.
2番の人は いろは先輩 強いって言ってもらって
Person number 2, say 'Iroha-senpai is strong'.
3番の人は いろは先輩 最強って言ってもらっていいですか？
Person number 3, say 'Iroha-senpai is the strongest', please?
まつり先輩がいるにも関わらず全員に先輩呼びをさせるいろは
Iroha making everyone call her senpai despite Matsuri being here.
いいよー オッケー
Sure, okay!
じゃあ1番の方から
Then, from number 1.
はい いきます
Yes, here I go!
いろは先輩 かっこいい！
Iroha-senpai, you're cool!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しいかもこれ
This might make me happy.
え、2番、2番
Eh, number 2, number 2.
いろは先輩 強い！
Iroha-senpai, you're strong!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しいかもこれ
This might make me happy.
言われたことないもん全然
I've never been told that at all.
いろは先輩... ちょっと怖い怖い
Iroha-senpai... wait, this is scary.
いろは先輩って最強ですよね？
Iroha-senpai is the strongest, right?
なんであとから攻めてるの？
Why are you attacking from behind?
先輩って言ってるのに！
Even though you're calling me senpai!
嬉しいけどなんか違う！
I'm happy but something's wrong!
なんか違くない！？
Isn't something wrong!?
なんかねっとりしてたよ
It was kind of slimy.
ごめんだったのに
Even though I said sorry.
なんでそんなねっとりしてるの？
Why is it so slimy?
嬉しいんですけどね
I'm happy though.
なんかねっとり圧があります
There's a slimy pressure.
初めて見た人生で、ねっとり圧
First time seeing slimy pressure.
王様なのに
Even though I'm the King.
嬉しかっただろ 王様
You were happy, weren't you, King?
1番と2番は嬉しかった
1 and 2 made me happy.
なんでだよ！
Why!
お返しで嬉しいんだよ おかしいだろ
I'm happy because of the return, it's weird.
ねっとりした
It was slimy.
よし じゃあ
Alright, then.
さっき歌ってないの あと二人ね
Two people haven't sung yet.
このメンタルで？
With this mental state?
一回任せる
I'll leave it to you once.
じゃあ二人で歌おう
Then, let's sing together.
よし じゃあこれにしよう
Alright, let's go with this.
これちょっと一人で歌うの不安なんで
I'm a bit anxious about singing this alone.
じゃあマツリに助けてもらいます
Then I'll have Matsuri help me.
さっき助けてもらったからな
Since I was helped earlier.
ここからカラオケに帰っていけるテンションなのか
Can we get back into the karaoke mood with this?
Three, two, one, zero!
ここで登場
Here is my entrance
見てなさい 私の本気
Watch my true strength
スリルと美意識で
With thrills and aesthetic consciousness
勝つのよ必ず
I will definitely win
優しげな言葉ささやく
Whispering gentle words
偽の可愛さじゃなくて
It’s not some fake cuteness
冷たく強く守らなきゃ
I have to protect them coldly and strongly
大切なモノ達 弱きモノ達
Important things, weak things
私は誰でしょう?
Who am I?
知りたくなったでしょう?
You wanted to know, right?
ならば恋かも
Maybe it’s love
私の中には秘密があるとして
Assuming there are secrets within me
それを君は どうするの
What will you do about that?
It's soldier game
また会えた時 訊こうかな
Maybe I’ll ask when we meet again
かっこいい！ やったー！
So cool! Yay!
動き、動きやめて
Stop the movement, stop it
Three, two, one, zero!
つぎの作戦
Next strategy
見てなさい 私は本気
Watch me, I'm serious
シグナル 受けとめて
Catch the signal
未来を頂く
I'll take the future
微笑みよりも甘いのは
What's sweeter than a smile...
嘘が招いた涙よ
are tears brought by lies
儚さ脆さ隠してる
Hiding the transience and fragility
大切なモノなの 弱きモノなの
It's something important, something weak
私と来るでしょ？
You'll come with me, right?
触れたくなったでしょう？
You wanted to touch me, right?
すでに恋だよ
It's already love
私といつかは戦うべき相手
The opponent I must fight someday
それは君の理性かも
Maybe that's your reason
I'm soldier heart
負けないからね It's soldier game
I won't lose, it's soldier game
いまが勝負よ！ 私は誰でしょう？
Now's the showdown! Who am I?
知りたくなったでしょう？
You've become curious, haven't you?
ならば恋かも
Then it might be love
私の中には秘密があるとして
Assuming I have a secret inside me
それを君は
What will you do?
私と来るでしょ？ 触れたくなったでしょう？
You'll come with me, right? You wanted to touch me?
すでに恋だよ
It's already love
私といつかは戦うべき相手
Someday you'll be the opponent I must fight
それは君の理性かも
That might be your rationality
It's soldier game また会えたのに
It's soldier game, even though we met again
I'm soldier heart
おー、かっこいい！
Oh, so cool!
最高！ みんなで横揺れ...
Awesome! Everyone swaying side to side...
何これ、幸せすぎたわ。
What is this? I was too happy.
夢が叶っちゃったわ...
My dream came true...
よし、じゃあ次は風真だね。
Alright, next is Kazama, right?
もうそろそろ回復したんじゃない？
Should be recovered by now, right?
あ、はい！ 回復しました！
Ah, yes! I've recovered!
じゃあこれにしよっか、20番。
Then let's go with this one, number 20.
おー、いい！
Oh, nice!
怖い、この人たち！
These people are scary!
なんてとこ来ちゃったんだ...
What kind of place have I come to...
助けてー！
Help me!
SOSを叫んだほうがいいんじゃないかと思ってました
I was thinking I should shout for SOS.
よし、じゃあ頑張って！
Alright, then do your best!
最後、盛り上げるわ！
I'll pump it up at the end!
じゃあ行きます！ 使います！
Then I'll go! I'll use it!
今なんじゃない？
Isn't it now?
メラメラとたぎれ
Burning like a flame
眠っているだけの正義
Justice just sleeping
こんな僕も君のヒーローになりたいのさ
I want to be your hero too
かっこいい君には 僕じゃ頼りないのかなんて
To the cool you, am I unreliable?
そりゃそうだよな
That's right
だって今もこうして迷ってる
Because even now I'm lost like this
手をとってくれないか
Won't you take my hand?
ギブとテイクさ
Give and take
君が僕のヒーローだったように
Just like you were my hero
今なんじゃない？
Isn't it now?
メラメラとたぎれ
Burning like a flame
こんな僕にも潜む正義が
Justice lurking inside me too
どうしようもない
Helplessly
衝動に駆られて
Driven by impulse
ほら気付けば手を握っている
Look, I'm holding your hand before I know it
いったいぜんたい そんなに荷物を
What on earth, all that luggage
背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Where are you going, carrying it all?
ねえねえ待って
Hey hey wait
僕にちょっと預けてみては？
Why not leave it with me for a bit?
信じてばかりの僕と
Me who just keeps believing
信じることが怖い君と
And you who are afraid of believing
どちらが正しいのかなんて
No one knows which is right
誰にも分からないさ
No one knows
僕らだけの世界
A world just for us
補い合えた暁には
At the dawn when we've complemented each other
同じ夢を見たい
I want to see the same dream
君はかっこいいと苦しめて
What made you suffer and left you all alone
ひとりぼっちにさせたのは
By saying you're cool
少し僕のせいなんだよな
Is a little bit my fault
ごめんね
I'm sorry
だけど見るべきはリアルだ
But what we should look at is reality
今こそ僕が救うんだ
Now is the time I will save you
抱えないで 信じて
Don't carry it all, believe me
頼ってほしいんだ
I want you to rely on me
今なんじゃない？
Isn't it now?
メラメラとたぎれ
Burning like a flame
こんな僕にも潜む正義が
Justice lurking inside me too
どうしようもない
Helplessly
There's no other way
衝動に駆られて
Driven by an impulse
ほら気付けば手を握っている
Look, before I knew it, I was holding your hand
ほっとけない
I can't leave you alone
そんなに荷物を
With all that baggage
背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Where are you going, carrying it all?
ほんのちょっと
Just a little bit
僕にちょっと預けてみては？
Why not let me carry some of it?
こんな僕も
Even someone like me
君のヒーローになりたいのさ
wants to be your hero
アイツを愛す覚悟が
If you're ready to love that person,
できてるなら叫べ！
Then shout it out!
あいす！ (あいす！)
Aisu! (Aisu!)
俺のあいす！
My Aisu!
あいす！ (あいす！)
Aisu! (Aisu!)
俺のあいす！
My Aisu!
グーチョキパーで
With Rock, Paper, Scissors,
何作ろう？ 何作ろう？
What shall we make? What shall we make?
右手をパーで 左手もパーで
Right hand is Paper, left hand is Paper too...
君に会いたい！ ねえ会いたい！
I want to see you! Hey, I want to see you!
ねえ会いたい！ ねえ会いたい！ ねえ会いたい！
Hey, I want to see you! Hey, I want to see you!
いつでも i に KITE!
Come to 'i' anytime!
運命の出アイ 誓うポライ
Fated encounter, I swear to the future
不眠不休で遊ぼうぜ！
Let's play through the night without sleep!
フルパワーで飛べ！
Fly at full power!
会いたい！ ねえ会いたい！ ねえ会いたい！
I want to see you! Hey, I want to see you!
今すぐ i に KITE!
Come to 'i' right now!
届け アイぼっちライ
Reach them, my lonely love
フッきって騒ぎ散らせ
Break free and cause a ruckus
新規手もあげて (ハイハイ！)
New fans, put your hands up! (Hi-Hi!)
古参もあげて (ハイハイ！)
Old fans, put them up too! (Hi-Hi!)
スタッフさんもあげて！！！ (いぇーい！)
Staff members, raise them high!!! (Yay!)
心も体も飛び跳ねる
Heart and body both jumping high
君も今日からアイライファー
From today, you're an i-Lifer too
いつまでもずっとアイライファー
Forever and ever, an i-Lifer
アイドルファンって こんなに体力使うんだね
Being an idol fan takes so much energy...
痩せたわー
I lost weight!
コール側が楽しい
Doing the chants is so fun!
いい曲だこれ
What a great song.
じゃあ次、歌っていただくのは...
Now, for our next performer...
風真いく？ この流れで？
Kazama, you going? After that?
タンバリン持ったところ申し訳ないが
I'm sorry, you've got the tambourine and everything...
確かにこのメンバーでいくとしたらござるなのかい
True, in this lineup, I guess it has to be de-gozaru.
よし、じゃあ頑張って歌っていただきましょう
Alright, let's have her give it her best!
怪獣の花唄 大好き
Monster's Flower Song, I love it!
いい曲だこれ 大好き
It's such a good song, I love it.
やばい今日に限って低い声が全然出...
Oh no, today of all days, my low notes won't...
チューニング チューニング
Tuning, tuning...
テンション上げたからね
I got too pumped up.
思い出すのは君の歌
What I remember is your song,
会話よりも鮮明だ
It's clearer than any conversation.
どこに行ってしまったの
Where did you go?
いつも探すんだよ
I'm always looking for you.
思い出すのは君の歌
What I remember is your song,
歌い笑う顔が鮮明だ
I see your face singing and smiling so clearly.
君に似合うんだよ
That suits you so well,
ずっと見ていたいよ
I want to keep looking at you.
でも最後に見たいのは
But the last thing I want to see is...
きっともう君の夢の中
I bet it's already inside your dream.
もう一度 また聞かせてくれよ
One more time, let me hear it again,
聞きたいんだ
I want to hear it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
Make more noise, monster's song,
まだ消えない夢の歌唱えて
Sing the dream song that hasn't faded yet.
君がいつも歌う怪獣の歌
The monster's song you always sing,
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
It hasn't faded, I find myself humming it.
思い出すのは君がいた
I remember that you were there,
ギター持ってる君がいた
You were there with your guitar.
忘れられないんだよ
I can't forget it,
だから僕が歌うよ
So I will sing it now.
でも最後に見たいのは
But the last thing I want to see is...
きっともう君の夢の中
I bet it's already inside your dream.
もう一度 また聞かせてくれよ
One more time, let me hear it again,
聞きたいんだ
I want to hear it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
Make more noise, monster's song,
まだ消えない夢の歌唱えて
Sing the dream song that hasn't faded yet.
君がいつも歌う怪獣の歌
The monster's song you always sing,
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
It hasn't faded, I find myself humming it.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で
The falling past is vivid,
見せたい未来は繊細で
The future I want to show is delicate,
すぎてく日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are oblivious to the passing days.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で
The falling past is vivid,
見せたい未来は繊細で
The future I want to show is delicate,
すぎてく日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are oblivious to the passing days.
ねえ、もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
Hey, make more noise, monster's song,
まだ消えない夢の歌唱えて
Sing the dream song that hasn't faded yet.
君がいつも歌う怪獣の歌
The monster's song you always sing...
口ずさんでしまうよ
I'll end up humming along.
ねぇ、僕ら
Hey, we...
（眠れない夜に）手を伸ばして
Reach out to the (sleepless nights),
（眠らない夜を）また伸ばして
Stretching out the (nights without sleep) again,
（眠くない まだね）そんな日々でいたいのにな
I want to stay in days like those (I'm not sleepy yet).
懲りずに（眠れない夜に）手を伸ばして
Unwearied, reach out to the (sleepless nights),
（眠らない夜を）また伸ばして
Stretching out the (nights without sleep) again,
（眠くない まだね）そんな夜に歌う 怪獣の歌
Singing the Kaiju's song in a night like this.
（落ちていく過去は鮮明で）
(The falling past is vivid,)
見せたい未来は繊細で
The future I want to show is delicate,
すぎていく日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are insensitive to the passing days.
王様ゲームの時のがちゃんとシーンになっててよかった
I'm glad the King Game part turned into a proper scene.
今日はかっこいいって言ってもらえそう
I think people will call me cool today.
かっこよかった、かっこよかった！
You were cool, so cool!
ちょっと棒なのやめてもらっていい？
Can you stop being so monotone?
歌はかっこよかった
The singing was cool.
可愛い、エモかったね
Cute, it was emotional, right?
よし、じゃあ次どっちいくかな
Alright, who's going next?
いきます！
Here I go!
わー、大好き！
Wow, I love this!
本当に好き！
I really love it!
緊張する、頑張る！
I'm nervous, I'll do my best!
神曲！
God-tier song!
神曲来ちゃう！神曲来ちゃう！
A god-tier song is coming! It's coming!
頑張る！さすがにペンライト
I'll do my best! Definitely need penlights.
「キスをあげるよ」 今気付いた想い
"I'll give you a kiss" These feelings I just noticed,
どんな言葉でも 足りないから
Because no matter what words I use, they're not enough.
One, two, three, four!
当たり前すぎるぐらい 友達の時間が長かったせいで
Because we've been friends for so long,
あなたのクセや性格だって 他の子より知ってんの
I know your habits better than anyone else.
Ha~ 意気地なしで
Ha~ Being a coward...
恥ずかしがり屋な
...and a shy person,
あなたをもう待ってられないの
I can't wait for you any longer.
「キスをあげるよ」 今さら「好き」なんて
"I'll give you a kiss" Saying "I love you" now...
言葉より キキメあるでしょ？
...is more effective than words, right?
あなたにだけは そっと教えてあげる
Only to you, I'll quietly tell you.
胸の奥 小さいつぼみのぬくもり
The warmth of a small bud deep inside my heart.
時々甘えてみたり
Sometimes acting spoiled,
拗ねてみたり そんな作戦らしくない
Acting petulant... such tactics aren't like me.
か弱きオトメじゃ勝てないの この恋だけは負けられない
A frail maiden can't win; I can't lose this love.
Ha~ 鈍感なあなたのこと
Ha~ You, who are so insensitive,
振り向かせたいから 勝負かけるの
I want you to notice me, so I'm taking a chance.
「キスをあげるよ」 『愛してます』なんて
"I'll give you a kiss" Saying "I love you"...
言葉より 魅力的でしょ？
...is more charming than words, right?
聞こえちゃうぐらい 速くなるドキドキ
My heart is beating so fast you can almost hear it.
初恋は サイダーみたいに弾ける
First love pops like cider.
“友達同士” そんな境界線
The boundary of being "just friends",
今すぐに 飛び越えたいの
I want to leap over it right now.
「キスをあげるよ」 今さら「好き」なんて
"I'll give you a kiss" Saying "I love you" now...
言葉より キキメあるでしょ？
...is more effective than words, right?
あなたにだけは そっと教えてあげる
Only to you, I'll quietly tell you.
胸の奥 小さいつぼみのぬくもり感じて
Feel the warmth of a small bud deep inside my heart.
小さいつぼみのぬくもり感じて
Feeling the warmth of a small bud
おおー！最高！神曲！
Whoa! That was the best! A god-tier song!
神曲や... 神曲やな...
A god-tier song... It really is a god-tier song...
本当に最高。
Truly the best.
これちまう！これちまうぞー！
This is it! This is the one!
よし、じゃあ次 Z だ。
Alright, next is Z.
Z？はい、歌いましょう。
Z? Yes, let's sing it.
13番？
Number 13?
うん、13。
Yeah, 13.
一緒に歌いますか、これ。
Shall we sing this together?
私踊ってあげる。懐かしいの。
I'll dance for you. This is nostalgic.
みんなで歌お！みんなで！
Let's all sing! Everyone!
みんなで歌いますか。
Shall we all sing together?
私もマイクを持つか。
Should I hold a mic too?
振り付け、夏祭り。
The choreography is Natsumatsuri style.
うちらはバックダンサーね。
We'll be the back dancers.
二人のデュエット聞きたい。
I want to hear your duet.
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let a romance scandal escape
消してあげる
I'll erase it for you
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
Oath! If I become the president...
人の男にちょっかいかける女は 島流しにします！
I'll exile any woman who meddles with other people's men!
ヘソから電気を流します。
I'll send electricity through their belly buttons.
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵 センセーショナル クローズアップ
Da-da-da, audacious, sensational, close-up
D, D, D, Don't cry やるぜ徹底的にリサーチ
D, D, D, Don't cry, I'll do thorough research
大嫌い？ しょうがない？
Hate it? Can't be helped?
クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイ
Trash is a disease, bye-bye-bye
権力！財産！地位名声！！
Power! Wealth! Status and Fame!!
なんにもないけど 裁きたいでしょ？
You have nothing, but you want to judge, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
Da-da-da, if I become the president
まずは君を捕まえるね
First, I'll catch you
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything
誰ですかあの女（いやぁ〜）
Who is that woman? (Nooo~)
ダメですか
Is it no good?
そうですか（あちゃ〜）
I see... (Oh boy...)
ロマンス of 不祥事 逃がさない 消してあげる
I won't let a romance scandal escape, I'll erase it
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ プレジデント
Sil-vous-pre-pre President
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
Oath! If I become the president...
「ただの仕事の付き合いだよ！」って言う奴は 二度と働けなくしてやります
Those who say "It's just for work!" will never work again!
宣誓！以下略！「いや向こうが強引でさ〜」
Oath! Rest omitted! "No, they were just pushy~"
っていう男の口には レジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
In the mouths of men who say that, I'll pour resin and harden it!
み・み・み・密着 まるでドン・ファン気取り スキャンダラス
Mi-mi-mi, close contact, acting like a Don Juan, scandalous
ま・ま・ま・末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクープね
Ma-ma-ma, street price, a scoop for a deadbeat
愛はない？ 理由じゃない
No love? That's not a reason
悪くないのね はいはいはい
Not your fault, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah
軽薄！のうのう！いけしゃあしゃあ！！
Frivolous! Carefree! Shameless!!
なんにもないとか ありえないでしょ？
Say you have nothing? That's impossible, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね
Da-da-da, even if I become the president
たぶん君は変わらないね
You probably won't change
しらっととぼけて
Playing dumb with a straight face
のらりくらりかわすのね
Eluding me ever so casually
デートですか こんばんは（うわぁ〜）
Is it a date? Good evening (Whoa~)
本気ですか
Are you serious?
そうですか（ほちゃ〜）
I see... (Oh boy...)
情熱とは不注意
Passion is carelessness
微熱も消してしまいたい
I want to erase even this slight fever
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
Da-da-da, if I become the president
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll catch you for real
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you spill everything
どこですか 今あんた（おやぁ〜？）
Where are you now? (Oh~?)
見っけちゃった バレちゃった（おらー！）
Found you, you're caught (Hey!)
夜道にはご用心
Be careful on the night roads
さよなら代わりに銃声
Instead of a goodbye, a gunshot
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ プレジデント
Sil-vous-pre-pre President
最高！最高！
That was the best! The best!
よかったですねー！
That was great!
そろそろ時間か？
Is it about time?
まつりもお腹空いてきた、こんだけ動いたら。
Matsuri is getting hungry too, after moving this much.
え、じゃあもうご飯食べに行きますか。
Well then, shall we go eat?
ご飯何食べに行こうかな。
I wonder what we should go eat.
寿司？寿司食べたい！
Sushi? I want to eat sushi!
じゃ、見てくれたみんなもありがとう。
Well, thanks to everyone who watched too.
よし行くか。
Alright, let's go.
リリカ、壁にならなくていいの？
Ririka, don't you need to become the wall?
じゃあみんなで、ほら、一回壁になりますか。
Then everyone, let's all become the wall for once.
壁の気持ちを知ってください、一回ね。
Please know the feelings of the wall, just once.
どうすか、居心地いいですよね、ここ。
How is it? It's comfortable here, isn't it?
いやなんか、すっごい... 落ち着くんだけど。
Yeah, it's actually... really calming.
や、落ち着きますよね、これ。
Yeah, this is calming, isn't it?
じゃ、じゃあ、二人で残ってて。
Well, then, you two stay here.
ゼータ、じゃあお寿司食べに行こ？
Zeta, then let's go eat sushi?
えっ？ うん。
Eh? Yeah.
お寿司食べに行こ？
Let's go eat sushi?
行こ！
Let's go!
寿司食べたーい！
I want to eat sushi!
なんか... そんな感じが...
Somehow... that's the vibe...
あ、じゃあ一緒にこれからも、こうやって画面見ててくれ...
Ah, then please continue watching the screen like this with me...
えっ、いますよね？
Eh, you're here, right?
うん、いる。
Yeah, I'm here.
いましょう。うん。
Let's stay. Yeah.
これから、今年は...
From now on, this year...
仲良くなりましょうね。
let's be close.
よし。じゃあ、行こ！
Alright. Then, let's go!
寿司食べに行くぞー！
Let's go eat sushi!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
カラオケ覗き見！？
Karaoke Peek!?